Jason Mabry

* For an online version of this document with clickable links, please visit http://web.mymabry.com.

\: 276.632.2490

1: 276.734.2747

✓: jmabry@mymabry.com

I am a dedicated IT professional with nearly a decade of experience in the field. I possess a passion for all things web related. I enjoy designing and developing user friendly web sites and applications. I also have extensive experience in web server configuration and maintenance on multiple server operating systems. I am a lifelong learner who enjoys a challenge and thrives on optimizing the experience for each end user.



Skills	Servers/Infrastructure/Cloud	Development	Other
	Active Directory Administration	HTML5/CSS	3D design and
	 Group Policy, File & Print Services, 	 JavaScript 	printing
	RADIUS/LDAP, AVG	Ruby on Rails	 Troubleshooting
	Google Apps Administration	Elixir/Phoenix	 Problem Solving
	Office 365 Administration	 WordPress 	 Works well
	 VMWare 	• PHP	individually or on
	 Meraki Wireless Networking and MDM 	• GitHub	a team
	 Cisco Routing and Switching 		
	Linux Server Administration		
	Web server configuration and		
	maintenance		

http://web.mymabry.com/

Experience

Web Work

Website Developer — 2010-present

- Wordpress Samples:
 - http://www.greenlivingresale.com
 - http://www.martinsvillehugos.com
 - http://www.checkeredpig.com
 - http://www.stonemcc.com
 - http://www.fixnyourpc.com

HTML/CSS Site Samples:

- o http://www.starfoodproducts.com
- o http://team1262.net

• Web Application Samples:

- http://mockapplication.pgsmst.com
 - Sign in email: jason@mymabry.com
 - Sign in password: TestAdmin
- http://aet-staging.newcollegeinstitute.org
 - Sign in email: jmabry@mymabry.com
 - Sign in password: foobar
- https://wilbur-staging.herokuapp.com/
- o https://intense-headland-35083.herokuapp.com/
 - currently under construction

FixnYourPC

Server Administrator — 2014-present

- Windows and Linux server installation and maintenance
- Responsible for all aspects of Wordpress based web hosting for several area businesses
- Customization of Wordpress themes
- Manage SmarterMail email server
- Owncloud installation and management

Piedmont Governor's School

IT Specialist — 2012-present

- Research and recommend potential purchases of technology.
- Responsible for the maintenance of all technology including, laptops, desktops, Kindles, iPads, printers, etc.
- Responsible for the maintenance of and updates to school website.
- Designed and developed an online application system for prospective students of the Governor's School.
- Set up and maintain Google Apps for Education domain services.
- Oversee all aspects (design, printing, maintenance, etc) of 3D printing within the school.
- Assist with instruction in Cyber Security.
- Aid in field trip activities for visiting students.

New College Institute *IT Specialist/Systems Administrator* — 2012-present

- Highly involved with the formulation of a Service Delivery Catalog and subsequent Disaster Recovery Plan for all services.
- Responsible for the administration and maintenance of an Active Directory Domain including ADDS,
 DNS, DHCP, DFS, WSUS, and Antivirus
- Responsible for a complex network, consisting of Cisco and Meraki wireless and wired technologies.
- Instrumental in upgrading our domain from Windows 2003 functional level to Windows 2008.
- Integral in the migration of several aging physical servers to a virtualized environment using VMware ESXi servers.
- Maintain and troubleshoot Polycom Video Tele-conferencing system and complex AV room setups controlled by Extron/Crestron controllers.
- Implemented Nagios monitoring service that monitors network devices and notifies IT staff if there is a problem.
- Responsible for the migration, configuration, and maintenance of Microsoft's Office 365 for Education.
- Configured and implemented an off-site backup/disaster recovery plan using Amazon's S3/Glacier services to store weekly VM server backups.

• Highly involved with the IT and infrastructure planning of a 50,000 square foot educational facility that opened in 2014.

Member of several committees including Technology, Marketing, and Security/Safety.

Henry County Public Schools

Computer Technician — 2006-2012

- Responsible for the upkeep and maintenance of all technology in two middle school buildings where technology is a major part of education.
- Administrator of large Active Directory Domain, including designing and implementing Group Policies for managing domain computers and users.
- Implemented network-based computer imaging system to streamline configuration.
- Implemented network monitoring system that sends email and SMS notifications when network equipment is down or malfunctioning.
- Instrumental in planning and implementing a mass deployment of Apple iPads to students, faculty, and administrators.
- Administrator of Google Apps for Education domain services.
- Responsible for customization and administration of Student Information System servers and web application.

Education

Radford University

Degree: Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

Concentration: Software Engineering

Patrick Henry Community College

Degree: Associate of Applied Science, Information Systems Technology

Concentration: Programming

References

Janet Copenhaver

Former Director of Technology and Innovation, Henry County Public Schools

http://web.mymabry.com/

email: jqcope63@gmail.com

phone: (276) 647-1234

Jason Draper

Developer, thoughtbot

email: draper@thoughtbot.com

phone: (276) 252-0258

Kenny Webster

Owner, FixnYourPC

email: kenny@fixnyourpc.com

phone: (276) 732-4695